Get some action.
Charlie's Angels is a action, comedy, adventure film directed by McG.
The captivating crime-fighting trio who are masters of
disguise, espionage and martial arts are back!
When a devious mastermind embroils them in a plot to destroy individual privacy, the Angels,
aided by their loyal sidekick Bosley, set out to bring down the bad guys.
But when a terrible secret is revealed, it makes the
Angels targets for assassination.
Natalie Cook, played by Cameron Diaz.
Dylan Sanders, played by Drew Barrymore.
Alex Munday, played by Lucy Liu.
John Bosley, played by Bill Murray.
Eric Knox, played by Sam Rockwell.
Roger Corwin, played by Tim Curry.
Charlie's Angels is a 2000 American spy action comedy film directed by McG in his feature
film directorial debut, and written by Ryan Rowe, Ed Solomon, and John August.
It is the first film in the Charlie's Angels trilogy, a continuation of the
television series of the same name created by Ivan Goff and Ben Roberts.
Unlike the original series, the film features more comic elements.
The movie stars Cameron Diaz, Drew Barrymore, and Lucy Liu as three
women working in a private detective agency in Los Angeles.
John Forsythe reprised his role as the unseen
Charlie's voice from the original series.
Bill Murray also stars as John Bosley, replacing David Doyle,
who played the role in the original series.
It also stars Sam Rockwell, Tim Curry and Kelly Lynch while Crispin Glover, Matt
LeBlanc, Luke Wilson and Tom Green appear in supporting roles.
The film was released on November 3, 2000, in the United States by Sony Pictures Releasing
under its Columbia Pictures label, and grossed $264.1 million worldwide.
The film received mixed reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of martial arts, undercover
agent, spy, secret agent, satire.
The tone is lighthearted and intense.